[Music]
[Applause]
but further missions
you [ __ ] what party with cut cut her
body in her barbecue dummies all over my
body
sending all over my buddy Carly got your
butt's all night [ __ ] I ain't gang name
baby chuckling and legs got the frame
one st. and st. I jump but Chuck gonna
change [ __ ] up a chicken the flame
pretty chicken made you upset good he
got brick state of saying hey pretty put
the [ __ ] on offset buddy it cardi big
rhinos offset credits if it made you
upset funny buddy got [ __ ] tape us a
clean credit to the [ __ ] on Austria cut
it cut it big brain on offset who gets
his notebook spot God looks like your
[ __ ] has the party card at six your
bits in the party guard who that be
dad's Martian guard who they don't pick
in the cut card who got the pricks in
the trust God and downs go ahead like a
[ __ ] wound up [ __ ] ass [ __ ] [ __ ]
will wanna be caught it but I'm MJ
moonwalking in a [ __ ] move walk into
your clique I'm moving walking in the
city with you kid move box in this [ __ ]
i fund the [ __ ] Bronx [ __ ] I
keep the pump in the trunk trunk picture
your bed to jump Chuck may lead your
[ __ ] in the stuff your [ __ ] want party
with cut cut here body and her barbecue
dummies all over my body
swimming all over
buddy cardi got your books all night big
swing gang legs chuckling legs got the
frame one st. and st. I jump but
chucking the chain [ __ ] up a chicken the
flame pretty chicken made you upset good
he got big State upstate ready critic
put the [ __ ] on awesome buddy it cardi
big bang on offset credits if it made
you upset buddy got [ __ ] tape up safely
credit for the [ __ ] Oh Oscar cut it cut
it big bang on offset dish when a party
with a sad 21 senator on Severson has
yeah high-end cars in fashion 21 don't
eat puts on fasting God all my blood my
brother creeping [ __ ] I'm dripping how
you tripping told the waitress ain't
tipping not like hot sauce on my cheek
uncle I put a rubber off and I put hot
sauce on her titty
I'm in a Bentley trust she keep on
sucking like his Tina :
howdy VBS is [ __ ] my spine work me
[ __ ] so bad I popped to modify your
party will cut cut here body in a
barbecue dummies all over my body
shining all over my body Carla got your
purse all night [ __ ] I ain't gay man
chuckling a.length got the frame i won
st. a jumper took in the taint [ __ ] up a
chicken the flame pretty sick it made
you upset
could he got big State upstate could you
put the [ __ ] on offset buddy it cardi
Big Bang knows offset credits if it made
you upset funny buddy got [ __ ] tape up
say hey could you put the [ __ ] on a
straight cut it cut it big bang on
concepts step in this bitch's [ __ ] [ __ ]
up a check in to pitch us to the coop in
them inches I [ __ ] up a back at the
pentia [ __ ] up back in a minute
we know a trip like this who you know
build like this I'm not sure like a dupe
pull up the puppet show coupe I've been
there too oh they said you basically
love the Royal with dumbest a predator
satanic embrace it I got your picture
she naked eye son the cake when I pick
it
I'm such a lays in the range I'll put
the dip of the brand so page updates for
your main stuff but the chap with the
fam I set them cardi B cardi a brand
your [ __ ] won't party with cut cut here
body and her re dummies all over my body
[ __ ] all over my body cardi got your
boots all night [ __ ] you ain't game you
a better truck laying the legs got the
Train I was insane insane I jump but
took in the tank
[ __ ] up a chicken the flame pretty
chicken made you upset could he got rich
day of saying hey
to the casino all set buddy Accardi big
bang on offset credits it made you upset
buddy got rich de-puff say Freddy put in
for the [ __ ] of Australia Cuddy big
brain or constant
[Music]